<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Battery on Kevin&#39;s Codex</title>
    <link>https://klee30810.github.io/paper_review/battery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Battery on Kevin&#39;s Codex</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 05:35:22 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://klee30810.github.io/paper_review/battery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Li-ion battery materials: present &amp; future</title>
      <link>https://klee30810.github.io/paper_review/battery/nitta2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 07:38:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klee30810.github.io/paper_review/battery/nitta2015/</guid>
      <description>Nitta, N., Wu, F., Lee, J. T., &amp;amp; Yushin, G. (2015). Li-ion battery materials: present and future. Materials today, 18(5), 252-264.  Abstract   This review covers key technological developments and scientific challenges for a broad range of Li-ion battery electrodes materials : lithium cobalt oxide (LCO), lithium nickel cobalt manganese oxide (NCM), lithium nickel cobalt aluminum oxide (NCA), lithium iron phosphate (LFP), lithium titanium oxide (LTO) and others are contrasted with that of conversion materials, such as alloying anodes (Si, Ge, Sn, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Li-Ion Rechargeable Battery: A Perspective</title>
      <link>https://klee30810.github.io/paper_review/battery/goodenough2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 05:35:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klee30810.github.io/paper_review/battery/goodenough2013/</guid>
      <description>The Li-Ion Rechargeable Battery: A Perspective  Author : Kyungmin Lee Thesis : Li-Ion Battery is hot trend of technology with its cathode, anode, electrolyte, and separation membrane. Citation : Goodenough, J. B., &amp;amp; Park, K. S. (2013). The Li-ion rechargeable battery: a perspective. Journal of the American Chemical Society, 135(4), 1167-1176.  Abstract   Each cell of a battery stores electrical energy as chemical energy in two electrodes, a reductant (anode) and an oxidant (cathode)  separated by an electrolyte that transfers the ionic component of the chemical reaction inside the cell and forces the electronic component outside the battery  The chemical reaction of a rechargeable battery must be reversible on the application of a charging I and V.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
