<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investment_valuation on Kevin&#39;s Codex</title>
    <link>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investment_valuation on Kevin&#39;s Codex</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:41:26 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Introduction</title>
      <link>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/chap1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:41:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/chap1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Valuation Philosophical basis for valuation   A postulate of sound investing is that an investor does not pay more for an asset than its worth. Consequently, perceptions of value have to be backed up by reality, which implies that the price paid for any asset should reflect the cashflows that it is expected to generate.  Generalities about Valuation  1. Since valuation models are quantitative, valuation is objective  the inputs leave plenty of room for subjective judgments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Approaches to Valuation </title>
      <link>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/chap2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:41:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/chap2/</guid>
      <description>Approaches to Valuation 1. Discounted Cashflow Valuation   The the value of an asset to the present value of expected future cashflows on that asset the value of any aset is the present value of expected future cashflows that the asset generates  \( value\ =\ Σ^{t=n}_{t=1}\frac{CF_t}{(1+r)^t}\) r : reflecting the riskiness of estimated cashflows
 Categorizing DCF Models
 equity valuation - value just the equity stake in the business (residual cashflows after metting all expenses, reinvestment needs , tax obligations and net debt payments  \[value\ of\ equity = Σ^{t=n}_{t=1}\frac{CF\ to\ equity_t}{(1+k_e)^t}, k_e:\ cost\ of \ equity\]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Understanding Financial Statement</title>
      <link>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/chap3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:41:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/chap3/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Financial Statements  How valuable are the assets of a firm?
 How did the firm raise the funds to finance these assets?
 How profitable are these assets?
 How much uncertainty (or risk) is embedded in these assets?
  The Basic Account Statements  Balance Sheet  summarizes the assets owned by a firm, the value of these assets and the mix of financing, debt and equity, used to finance these assets at a point in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. The Basics of Risk</title>
      <link>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/chap4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:41:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/chap4/</guid>
      <description>The Basics of Risk Risk   the likelihood that we will receive a return on an investment that is different from the return we expected to make (not only low, but also high)  Equity Risk &amp;amp; Expected Return   a market where the marginal investor is well diversified, and the only market risk that will be rewareded  1. Defining Risk  variance, standard deviation : the spread of the actual returns around the expected return \(var=\frac{Σ(x_i-avg(x))}{n-1}\) skewness : the bias towards positive or negative returns kurtosis : fatter tails lead to higher kurtosis expected return : the opportunity in the investment stardard deviation or variance : the danger  → higher expected returns &amp;amp; more positive skewness is preferred</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chap5. Option Pricing Theory &amp; Models</title>
      <link>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/chap5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:41:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klee30810.github.io/finance/damodaran/investment_valuation/chap5/</guid>
      <description>Option Pricing Theory &amp;amp; Models  option  derive their value from the values of other assets. cash flows on the assets are contingent on the occurrence of specific events   Basics of Option Pricing   option : provides the holder with the right to buy or sell a specified quantity of an underlying asset at a fixed price (called a strike price or an exercise price) the holder can choose not to exercise the right and allow the option to expire  Call &amp;amp; Put Options : Description &amp;amp; Payoff Diagrams   Call option</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
